[music]
[музыка]
good afternoon, put a plus sign than what you started,
добрый день поставьте плюсик чем начатый
well, normally, the target burning form is
вы ну нормально целевую пригорания форму
not streaming and katsa, the program is something
не стримы и каца программа в чем-то
shock molding for my children and what
ударную формования моим детям и на какие
herbs and design on the hand thrown over well
травы и дизайн на руку накинутой ну так
so jokingly hand program both father’s studio
на шутку руку программа оба studio отца
I’m jumping in a frame on
я скача в рамочке на
starcraft that lives in edeline itself and
starcraft обитающий самом эделайн и
is called I don’t respect, but here the design is
называется я не уважаешь а тут дизайн
straight cool, I’m cola
стремитесь прям прикольные такие я cola
pacino andalan eraser buns, taking the
пачино ластиком андальским булочки взяв
mouse just naboo, you don’t cut
мыши просто набу ты ведь нет разрублю
such an icon, well, in short, that’s how it
такая иконочка ну короче так и
turned out  so good afternoon to everyone and
получилось так всем добрый день и и
today we have a good
сегодня у нас гуда
new country so I’m anand in general on the skin
ново краина так я ананд вообще у на кожу
once Budanov country like yes helping
раз буданова краина яко да помогая
Ukraine and we will still eat again
украине и мы будем еще есть снова ты на
v.t.  visiting about
богачу в.т. выездная про
friends of ukraine so who listens to us from
друзей украины так кто нас слушает из
countries that do not understand the ukrainian
стран которые плохо понимают украинский
language well today we will have another country
язык сегодня у нас еще одна страна будет
a guest that helps ukraine we
гость которая помогает украине мы на
will remember some
каждом стриме будем вспоминать некоторые
countries that help ukraine and something
страны которые помогают украине и что-то
about them about their former culture with their
про них про их прежнюю культуру при их
history  to learn new things and so I don’t-2
историю нового узнавать и так уж я пе-2
hard for you to guess the words shifted the
туго вам гру угадает слова перекладывала
soul to you
душе сподобалась вам
many times so that
много разу так что
everyone else has
всем дуже дуже дякую и
the same name and we also got a name and
имени тоже у нас подобралась и мы его
we develop it for you this eye don’t
нам развивать этому вы глазка не
forget 15 kilograms of a canal
забывайте 15 нами килограмм канальчик
for us so a subscriber on the rights  there may still be of
так подписчица на правах там еще может
course youtube yes there is there there are
это конечно youtube да есть там есть
blocks quieter just for the sake of sums of small fairy tales
блоки тише просто так суммы малый сказок
and a joke could be seen in this new channel
и шутку могла видно в этой новый канал
subscribe to my telegram channel
подпишитесь на мой телеграмм-канал
so that we have a connection even when there are
чтобы мы имели связь даже когда есть
problems with youtube or there will be some kind of
проблемы с youtube или будет какой-то
block there Russian  bots will attack
блок там российские боты будут атаковать
to close my
чтобы закрыть мой
youtube, so the subscriber for a kilogram is
youtube поэтому подписчица на килограмм
tied and
обовязково и
annealed today, and let it be given like this
отжиг сегодня а напустить давать так
ruff food without google will
перша питания без гугла
guess and I'm on the edge today there is our
угадает и я к краю на сегодня есть нашу
air the first question without google try
эфиру первый вопрос без гугла попробуйте
to guess which country is friendly to
угадать какая страна из дружественных
ukraine today the guest of our stream about
украине сегодня гость нашего стрима про
which country we will remember today
какую страну мы будем вспоминать сегодня
during the stream write your version
во время стрима напишите свою версию
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
this
этого
time  -two were on Thursday, so you, too,
раз-два было в четверг так что вы тоже
Lithuanian, we sorted it out in the last stream, immediately
литвы мы разбирали в прошлый стрим сразу
to them, skipping streams, those who came to
им их к пропуская стримы те кто пришел
this one, we miss a new lesson
этого той пропускаю мы новый урок
where are you with present,
куда ты with present
and
да и
today, the
сегодня
kids, he guessed it 1 gave and
детишек-то он угадал ее 1 дал и и
today is our
сегодняшняя наша
friendly  cry other than a guest of ukraine
дружная cry иное как гость украины
estonia estonia,
эстонии эстония и
etc.  real food without google on shift
т.п. реальный питания без гугла на сдвиг
put the order of the reef field to the ensign of
напустить порядок поля риф прапору
estonia from top to bottom write the order of the
эстонии сверху донизу напишите порядок
colors of the flag of estonia from top to bottom
цветов флага эстонии сверху вниз
today there is our air c estonia so
сегодня есть нашего эфиру c эстония так
amicably for ukraine kraina and parshat ki it
дружно для украины краина и паршат ки то
was 0 food gadot and scab food
было 0 питанием гадот а парша питания
without google view create from top to bottom
без гугла вид творить сверху вниз
order  kulev of estonia on a pro couple
порядок кулев эстонии на про паре
write from top to bottom what colors of the flag with
напишите сверху вниз какие цвета флага с
tone
тоней
we will be
мы буду
and you honor new ones, then we will not just
а ты честь новые то там мы не просто
be there, but there are 2 thousand rubles like that, so on
будем а там 2 тыс рублей такие так далее
we will be a thousand of us shining a mouse, I
мы будем нас тысяча светил мышь я уважаю
still respect for now and what
еще на ведь сейчас и какой там
annoyed him there  content can reach us there
раздражали его контент можно до нас там
you can reach us thousands sacredly even during
можно до нас тысячи свято даже во время
cool entertaining content you can
круто развлекательного контента можно
convey something correct something bright
донести что-то правильное что-то светлое
so before nab looking for your version some
так до наб ищет свою версию некие
order of hives ensign of estonia from top to
порядок ульев прапору эстонии сверху
bottom write your version and the
донизу напишите свою версию и
correct view comes to the studio after all
в студию приходит правильно вид по ведь
the correct view will appear st and not black
правильно вид появится ст и не черный
bill this blue black and white so here is a
билл этот синий черный и белый так вот
cool ensign Estonia view in the mirror the
классный прапор эстонией вид зеркале the
mouth of eastern &amp;
mouth of eastern &amp;
c blue black and white house to remember
c синий черный и белый дом запоминать
faces together with us with a wedge and by the name of Sean
лица дружно нам клином и по имени шон
with cotton wool and symbols and give out it didn’t turn
ватой и символы и выдать не перевернул
it over very painted and it was up to the mountain with its feet and
ее очень намалевал и ее до горы ногами и
that it bothers put a plus sign then the
что приедается поставьте плюсик то
inputs about the minuses of the tones of the year write
входов о минусах тонов года напишите
plus who guessed the correct arrangement of
плюсе кто угадал правильное расположение
colors minus who  didn’t guess who is
цветов минус кто не угадал кто
going to retake and
отправляется на пересдачу и
today we will have estonia so
сегодня у нас будет эстония так
he’s an initiative and debid from couples joking with yakunom
он же почином а дэbид из пар шутю якуном
caviar change puff in stock vidosiki
икра смены буф в запасе видосики
tied up to thousands need estonia 2nd that
повязаны до тысяч надо эстонии 2-ого что
bvb banya-bashi then didn’t know super
bvb баня-баши затем не знала супер
know that our stream account  new down
знаете что наш стрим счет новой вниз
our
наши
intellectual pink current found ores
интеллектуальный розовый ток нашли руды
tweakui so cool posts this fight us
tweakui так круто постам это борьба нам
know men estonia us up to helping
знать мужчин эстония нам до помогая
swim out and
выплынь и
blackmail ukraine and and friend kind let's
шантаж украину и и дружу добрый давайте
blow sodasan teak roller indica
подуем sodasan тиковый ролик индики
one will think and field flip flop
можно будет подумать и поле flip flop
good afternoon
добрый день
good afternoon and scourge
добрый день а бич
finally not  speak English it
наконец не говорите на английском
will come out where Norway themselves are on why
выйдет куда сами норвегии на почему этом
Russia is here
состоит россии тут
Norwegians themselves burn the panel
сами норвегии горите панель
to know and go through the contact  acts there in the
знать и заходишь через контакты там
capital of Russia and
столице россии а
you yourself come from where history will no longer
вы сами так родом откуда истории уже не
become by nationality, but I’m
станет стать по национальности но я
bigger Russians, well, how is my
более большие русские ну как у меня
grandmother from Ukraine, grandfather, connection and where
бабушка с украины дедушка связь и откуда
does the mayor’s speech come from with Russia, such moments the
с россией речи мэр такие моменты
brain explodes photo dude of energy and
взрывается мозг фото чувак энергии и
then once he comes he will give  and Estonia, but
тогда раз сам прихожу даст и эстонией но
wines are Russian, although I doubted the profit,
вин русский хотя я сомневался по выгоду
he is Russian and the
он русский и
grandmother is super and beautiful, and the
бабушка супер и красивым н и взрывается
brain explodes, we will continue the distance of the
мозг он мы продолжим даль
fields, we don’t know where exactly, I don’t remember
полей не знают куда точно не помню до
until visually this beard can,
того чтобы визуально может эта борода то
it seems to me that you are from
мне кажется что вы где-то родом из
somewhere  -something of the Caucasian republics because of a
каких-то кавказских республик из-за
beard until then they will not immediately be born black
бороды до то сразу не родятся черненький
yes there is Dagestan Chechnya
да там дагестан чечня
absolutely everything
абсолютно все так
as you feel about you could not be bad
как вы относитесь к вы не могли не плохо
very bad but what do you think why
очень плохо а как вы считаете почему
Russia attacked Ukraine
россия напала на украину
who the authorities agreed among themselves
кто власти между собой договорились
they were not authorities with  ours yes what they
их не власти с нашими да о чем они
agreed not only that russia
договаривались не только что россия от
wanted from us well I don’t know there und koch 14
нас хотела ну не знаю там und koch 14
years old he then
года он потом басу
came to russia the crimea occupied part of the
россию настал крым оккупировала часть
donbass as we were with him m  we can agree,
донбасса как мы с ним можем договориться
well, anyway, the neighbors can even from the sea
ну все равно соседи могу даже из моря
if I came to you, I wrested part of the room from you
если я вас я пришел отжал у вас часть
and then I propose that something else
комнаты и дальше предлагаю что еще
be agreed on how - she will
что-то договориться как - она
agree to be and agree on her own
договорится быть и свою договориться и
and take back the salt part of the room a
лет берете назад соли часть комнаты
little more protecting the territories of the room
чуть другое защиты территорий комнаты
absolutely  not myself not that comparison a
абсолютно не сам не то сравнение
little bit of salt here I live in my apartment
чуть-чуть соли вот я живу своей квартире
you also have people in yours live in their
вы в своей также есть народ живет своей
stage another in yours here one people
сцене другой в своей тут один народ
through their country took away
через свою страну отобрал у другого
part of the territory from another people but look look
народа часть территории но смотри смотри
I will explain to you this way I live in spain to me
я тебе объясню так я живу в испании мне
many times dances said [ __ ] and burns
много раз танцы говорили пизду и горит
to live all of my russia why did it stop
жить всю свою россию почему прекратился
this is my city this is all mine as it were
это мой город это тут все мои как бы
born why should i go know my
родился почему я должен ехать знать свою
say all this like or in estonian
говорят все это типа или по-эстонски
take speaks about you imagined only i
брать говорит о вы представляли только я
was born there take if but look
родился там брать если но смотри
why that's how you got to estonia at all
почему вот как ты вообще попал в эстонии
that's why you were born how did your parents
вот почему ты родился как ты родители
get to estonia i'm also dad was born
попали в эстонии я тоже папа родился
arranged what year
устроены каком году
i don't remember what it was 60 some  about the throat,
я не помню какое там 60 какой-то горло
so look, I’m in the fact that the Soviet Union occupied Estonia in the fortieth year, that the Soviet Union
так смотри я в том что советский союз
occupied
сороковом году оккупировал эстонии что
it as an independent state
него независимым государством советский
and started there with a
союз оккупировал его и начал туда с
visit by enemy Ukrainians, and so on
визитом вражеских украинцев и так дальше
why it
почему
occupied feasted for a period of a year, and
оккупировала пировали в сроком году а
how horrible Estonia was, the Soviet Union was
как попало эстонии советский союз
just a
просто
question so the war was on  the
вопрос так война была на начиналась
war began in what year the war began
война в каком году война началась
41 here is the forty-first so you are the great
41 вот сорок первым так вы великой
Patriotic if you count there and Estonia
отечественно если там считать а эстонии
in the fortieth got the Soviet Union of
в сороковом попала советский союз
Soviet Unions and bodies and 40 what kind of
советских союзов и тела и 40 каких
Baltics into the countries of the beam it turns out the
прибалтику на страны балки получается
fortieth Soviet Union captured
сороковом советский союз захватил
Estonia by taking other non-
эстонии по на возил туда других не
Estonians there so  Ukrainians there Russians
эстонцев так украинцев там россиян
Belarusians in the gases, and of course they
белоруса в газах а так конечно они
consider us occupiers,
считают оккупантами нас
we are for them to watch footage of several
мы для них смотреть кадры несколько
Lithuanians of Norway here
литовцев норвегии тут
somehow
как то
they arrived so Lithuania did not occupy
они приехали так литва не оккупировала
Norway so Norwegians although they let a
норвегию так норвежцы хотя отпускают
certain number of
определенное количество
foreigners go
иностранцев
Yes, well, not absolutely
да ну не абсолютно
there is a visa you need to get the truth you need anti-aircraft
есть визу надо получить правда зенитного
guns  Ukrainians could not  oh, there are
вам надо украинцы не смогли то есть есть
also countries with which Norway
и страны так с которыми у норвегии
simply has an agreement and a visa
просто есть договоренность а безвизовом
-free regime is true, that is, Norway
режиме правда то есть норвегия
voluntarily allows them certain
добровольно разрешают им определенным ли
citizens to be captured, so come there
че за пленным граждан так приезжай там
on certain conditions, there the
на определенных условиях там же
Soviet Union seized Estonia,
советский союз захватил эстонии
planted the Russian language there and
насаждал там русский язык так и
the population was brought there  not 100 for
завозился туда население не 100 на
eternity, and of course it will not be considered
извечные так и конечно не будет считать
occupiers, that is, it turns out, look at
оккупантами то есть получается смотри
your ancestors, well, there the father was still born in
твои предки ну там отец еще родился в
Spain, well, the grandfather was no longer worthy,
испании ну дед уже не был достойным
this is Spanish land and they must also
это испанская земля и надо их тоже
understand that they, as it were, survived this
понимает что они как бы ну пережили эту
occupation, they were there for how long  51 years
оккупацию они были там сколько 51 год
under the Soviet Union, yes, they consider the
под советским союзом да они считают
Ukrainians, Russians whom the Soviet Union brought there,
украинцев русских которых туда привез
they don’t consider them that this is
советский союз они не считают их что это
their land is absolutely true,
их не земле абсолютно верно
let’s say 100 doesn’t want to be from Russia there,
допустим 100 не хочет быть с россии там
but why would you want to be with Russia
но зачем как бы вы хотеть быть с россией
at the same time, hate it so much
в то же время этом сильно ненавидеть
it’s also clear to take a
тоже брать
dick that there will be something inside, this
ясен хуй что будет что-то внутри вот это
is the sovereign right to love someone to
есть суверенное право любить кого-то
hate, Estonia doesn’t want to  and she would
ненавидеть вот не хочет эстонии бы
absolutely hate Russia to the liking of the
совсем ненавидит она россии по душе
historically so developed she didn’t
исторически так сложившейся у не дала
give her this right and now you’re on fire you
тому это ее право и вот по ты горишь вы
said that in Estonian for a year in raids and
говорили что по-эстонски год в набеги и
you speak Norwegian and
ты говоришь по норвежским а
why did people know taught fashion and
почему люди знали научил fashion а
why, well, you even lope  with Norway at
почему ну ты ж скока даже с норвегией в
12 years old if you didn’t even put yourself in interesting things at 12 years old
12 лет если 12 лет ты даже не ставил
[music]
[музыка]
it is known by the soul you are bast because what is
его знают душа вы лыком ибо чем вот
such a problem savka chu people
такую проблему савка чу люди
they live in Estonia don’t want and
они живут в эстонии так не хочеть и
say Estonian new they need Russian
говорит эстонскую новую нужен им русский
language loves Estonia before coming  in
язык любит эстонии до приезжает в
norway, people are a victim of aunt rocky, he has
норвегии людына жертва на тетю рокки он
been living with norway for 12 years, but he does not want to
12 лет живет с норвегией но он не хочет
learn norwegian, he is not interested, i
учить норвежский не интересуется я в
look in, how can i do 12 lessons in liquid
заглядываюсь як можна 12 уроки в жидкой
in the region not and i will say we are broken by a
в крае не и я скажу нас разбитые
draft at this level,
черновиком на таком уровне
learn young up to 12 lessons blinded in a
научитесь молод до 12 уроки blinded in a
it grows up to 6th class
вырастает до 6 класс
bits for 3-4 rocks although it says
биты за 3-4 роки хотя говорит
special give the lines in the right way with them
особенными дай строки в нужном с ними
it is possible from the beer of these phenomena the intruder
можно из пива этих феномен нарушитель
I will go out to what the statues come true what
выйду к чему у статуи сбываются чему
people come to SBU composition like them chiklin
люди приезжают сбу состав как им чиклин
and so  and he doesn’t want to go to four places in
и так и не хочет он в четыре места в
my garden of lights
моем саду светиковой
in English, it’s good wool that everything is in
по-английски хорошо шерсть что все по
English discord and on display, but the
английски раздоры и на показе а норвежцы
Norwegians, for example, are local on the spot,
вот например местные на месте
you just work there somewhere on gas,
ты просто по работе там где-то по газу
you work to the hump,
работаешь до горба
that is, you just don’t  you live in the league,
то есть ты просто ты не живешь на лиге
in fact, you work there, so I live in a
по сути ты работаешь там так я живу во
dream, the government
сне на вид правительство получило вызовы
seems to have received calls, as it were, everything is Norwegian except for a passport,
уже как бы все норвежское кроме паспорта
that is, you just look like if the cops are not a
то есть вида у тебя просто если менты не
citizen,
гражданин
and you work there, you work, you
ты и ты там получается ты работаешь ты
work under certain conditions, then I
работаешь на определенных условиях то я
therefore  Norway let you in, for example,
поэтому тебя норвегии пустила например
just like that, it would not be allowed to live to you
просто так было бы не пустила жить к вам
from and the Internet you want to live with anyone
от и интернет хочешь живи у кого угодно
Europe if the law allows already
европу если закон позволяют уже
key minutes of gray conditions, that
ключевому минутами серого условия то
is, they won’t give them a life-long
есть не дадут им пожизненный вид на
residence permit, though I can’t everyone, not even
жительство правда я не могу всем даже не
everyone in a row, but you  given because you
всем подряд а тебе дали потому что ты
look at Riga is interesting, but what are you to
глянь риге интересен но что ты
gas industry specialists, for example,
специалистам газового отрасли например
but it turns out you live in a foreign country,
но получается ты живешь чужой стране вот
so you don’t want to learn the language there, well,
и ты не хочешь учить язык там ну а
why do you ask  then
почему вы просто
watch for free someone more a lot of
смотреть бесплатно кто-то больше много
visitors and everyone before who,
приезжих и все прежде которые там
let’s say, work somewhere there,
допустим где-то работают там есть
let’s say there is a company there, but of all the former ones,
допустим компания там но из всех прежних
there usually aren’t a single Norwegian there,
там обычно нет ни одного норвегов там
all the arrival of work forever there, ours is somewhere
все приезде работы навеки там наш где-то
in the offices there, such where therefore  a cocktail
в офисах там такой где поэтому коктейль
on the
на
fire a little bit we understand
огонь чуть чуть чуть понимаем
there is no contact with the local population under 12 years old
есть с местным населением до 12 лет не
you contact only with
контактируешь ты контактируешь только с
the same kind of employees why
такими же какие то и работниками почему
do I have a building I have a friend who
у меня есть здание у меня друг есть
periodically teach some word 0 but
периодически учат каким-то словом 0 но
there the local population of Norway do you
там местное население норвегии ты там
want to go there  at the end you get to know people
хочешь накида конце знакомишься с людьми
around from all over the world people here I don’t
вокруг со всего мира люди тут вот не
believe you’ll go here I don’t know let’s say
поверю вот пойдешь вот не знаю допустим
in one cabin one hundred percent like 50
в одном кабину сто процентов будто 50
different nationalities
разных национальностей
everything is so
настолько все
simple and interesting position without tony and
просто и интересная позиция без тони и
lived in Estonian but in Estonian you know
жил эстонский а вот и в эстонский знаете
yes it’s what  then the problem is
да она в чем тогда проблема в говоришь с
speaking with dancing talking in Estonian
танцем говорили разговоре по эстонски
what you didn’t want to see,
чего не хотели видеть а
well,
ну
write your versions to the wing neckline
напишите свои версии to the wing вырез
for being born in Estonia  and so the
на родывся в эстонии так сам
Russian-Ukrainian brush itself was brought in and
российско-украинский кисть внесенный и
there was not enough Estonia says the Estonian pestilence
не хватило эстонии говорит эстонскую мор
to let in his version of chu, but he, by
напустить своей версии чу а вот он по
nationality, sex Ukraine, slept Russian
национальности полу украине спал русский
was born in history because his parents
родился в истории потому что родители
got there dad ended up in Estonia in the
попали там папа попал в эстонии 60-х
60s and he didn’t want to talk in
годах и он не хотел разговаривать по
write in Estonian why he understands
эстонски напишите почему вот он понимает
he grew up in Estonia he knows
он вырос в эстонии знает эстонский язык
Estonian but doesn’t want to speak a
на но не хочет говорить на вашем doom
bunch of your doom then they are not only mine with us, as
кучу то они не только мои у нас нему как
if he spoke to himself,
бы образом как говорил про себя
well, it’s logical that they
ну так ну логично что они хотят в
want people to speak in history  from here I
истории чтобы люди говорили на с тут
don’t understand anyone like this in ukraine we
никого не понимаю такие вот в украине мы
want people to say spider fishing lines the
хотим до чтобы люди говорили паук лески
state language was the end look in
государственный язык был конец смотри на
ukraine if they come I’ll say
украине если придут скажу там уже
hello there let’s say the store paris
здравствуйте допустим магазине париж
will answer patches hello seeing that
ответят лоскутов здрасте видя что
we don’t have 18 in Russian now we have in
по-русски у нас сейчас нет 18 у нас в
Estonia  if you go to the store I’ll say
эстонии если ты пойдешь в магазине скажу
hello in Russian even before the war for a
на русском здравствуйте еще до войны
long time they specifically know
долго давно был они специально знаешь
they will be silent do not answer such
будут молчать ничего не отвечать такие
evil and  the fact that they considered the Russians
злые и потому что они считали русских
so slate we now also have to the
так шиффер у нас сейчас тоже у нас к
Russian language right now the relationship is changing
русскому языку щас отношения меняется
Russian-speaking people also
люди русскоязычный тоже как-то
look somehow differently because the language of the
по-другому смотрят потому что язык
occupiers, but these are those who were
оккупантов но это такие которых там
very hurt there, even I
очень сильно задело там идет даже сам
personally saw it here about oil  whoever went
лично видел тут о нефти кто ки заходил
there one soul, he says to the
там один душа он говорит
child I will only teach Ukrainian,
ребенку буду только украинскому учить
no Russian, I know that you are right,
никакого русского знаю что вы прям таки
yes, because the Russians are associated with the
да потому что русские ассоциируются с
invaders, the killers of quintana, with something
оккупантами убийцами кинтана чем-то
so bad fascism of the 21st century,
таким плохим фашизмом 21 века
well, let's run and then gouge the
хорошо давай побежала и дальше долбал
code
кода
, these are the problems we are more than  the damage and the
вот такие проблемы мы бо чем ущерб и
baltic republics on the outskirts of the beams are such
республиках балтии окраинах балки такие
problems themselves and in ukraine here on the weeds
сами проблемы и в украине вот на сорняки
here by the floor and hour to head for the
тут по полу и часу взять курс на вновь
bath principle again
принципа ванны хочу на русскость не хочу
they
русском что все говорили что все пушкина
read Pushkin there Lermontov is noisy I will speak there a
читали там лермонтова шумен заговорю там
Norwegian 12 lessons he has cheats well, damn it, I
норвежка 12 уроки у него читы ну блин я
don’t know, of course, we are loved to the stomach in the
не знаю я конечно любимые к животу мы в
previous  m she could in the heat let's say we
предыдущем она могла бы в жар скажем
need to grab at the moment for the music
нужно хватать у нас в момент к музыке
there are Syrians fishing ben say
есть сирийцы рыбачит бен говорить
Ukrainian wine earthly in scrap but well it
украинскую вин земное в лом а ну это
says well here living there 5 rocky cheesecakes
говорит ну тут живя там 5 рокки чизкейки
people are attacked then when such a
люди атакуются то ей когда такая
problem
проблема
decisively flock people to just
решительно стекаются люди на просто
herbs and  my monastic from the principle does not
травы и монастырский мой из принципа не
want the mentality okay so at once we have a
хочет менталитет окей так за раз у нас
buddha with google and
будда знов с google а
also get them sho who wants peter them
также добиться их шо кто хочет петр им
this channel from when you donations
этой канал с когда ты донаты ось
sent the axis to
посылали на
donations and
донат и
from above more precisely and we beat and food without
сверху точнее а мы побил и питания без
google dawuda folding food
гугла dawuda складная питания
develop  drunk more cmis estonia
развить пьяный больше cmis эстонии
wipe it one point for each
вытрем это один балл за каждую
correct type write 5 on and large
правильную вид напишите 5 на и больших
cities of estonia
городов эстонии
who is correctly called each city
кто правильно называется каждый город
gets 1 point i.e. if you name three out of
получает 1 балл то есть если вы три из
five correctly you get 3
пяти назовете правильно получаете 3
points on drag in one doctors not in one
балла на тащить в одном врачи не в одном
immediately five on  five carved by types,
сразу пять на пять резных по видам у
he will be swept up that he wrote out to
него буду на замела что выписала
ruin, but
загубить а вот в одном
in one message in 5 cities
в одном сообщении 5 городов
write
напиши
alexander franco here if I am in
александр франко сюда если я в
Kaliningrad after  dorovy from in German
калининграде по здоровы из по немецким
do not caress and climate
не ласкать и климата
test troll talin talinka linda klim polina we
талин талинка линда клим полина мы
don’t know anything on
ничего не знаем на
I know sprat places husband and I bush and
я-то знаю килька места муж и я буш и
tony
тони
give an accolade this trail name and 5
дать акколаду это тропа назвать и 5
greatest mist with Tonya who naming 1st
наибольших mist с тоней кто называя 1
place in the top five gets  point and that he
место в пятерке получает балл и что он
is a tracker us accept this fishing 5 to
это tracker us прими этот рыбалка 5 до
riga maria kovalchuk regatta in latvia plate
рига мария ковальчук регата в плите
also our friends so tallin tartu then i
тоже наши друзей так таллин тарту потом
don’t know any more in poland and men
больше не знаю в польше и мужчин они
today we don’t have poland today we have a
сегодня у нас не польша сегодня у нас
friendly outskirts to us in estonia and the
дружный окраина нам в эстонии и
right view  there will be such five
правильно вид появится вот такие пять
places
мест
in Tallinn tartu narva and kohtla-järve and pr
в таллин тарту нарва и кохтла-ярве и pr
for
на
25 places places on a bike so again
25 мест места на велике так вот опять
it was very and places my crumbs nicknames
это было очень и места мои крошки клички
more up to 40000 on the
бильше до 40000 на
councils of Estonia national nickname
советами эстонии национально кличке
more than a million give one million three hundred top,
больше миллиона дать миллион триста топ
that is, such a small  Is it the outskirts of
то есть такая невелик окраина ли она
lattissima mayonnaise, we can live and clean up our share of them ourselves, but even rich in Ukraine about the people in the Russian
багато украины о народе в российской
Federation, not waves up to 7, their games and and
федерации по не волны до 7 свои игры и и
sovereignty, a bunch of their Nikitich  I mean,
державности куча их никитич бишь
people who watch us from Russia,
люди которые нас смотрят из россии
especially there Tatars and Bashkirs and
особенно там татар и башкир и
Buryats, and so on, Estonia 1000 million
буряты и так дальше эстония 1000 миллион
three hundred people, of which there are
триста населения из них эстонцев там
about a million Estonians and they have their own country
около миллиона и они имеют свою страну
independently live normally live so they
независимо живут нормально живут так
manage their resources of theirs,
распоряжается своими ресурсами своей
let's say it's interesting because they see
скажем интересно так как они считают
fit therefore  when they say that there
нужным поэтому когда говорят что там
tatarstan without russia without
татарстан без россии без москвы
moscow levels out bashkiria will not survive to walk
нивелирует башкирия не выживет гулять
they are all a huge, huge
они вы же это все огромный-огромный
deceit
обман
so for the disintegration of the usa a couple of videos and
так за распадаемся сша пару видосики и
pass to find kvesh and our
передать до найти квеш и и наши
today’s basic lambada video on the right
сегодняшние справа базовую ламбада
is called out of politics
ролик называется вне политики
good afternoon
добрый день
how are you  the channel is called
как у вас канал называется
which channel and like it’s a streamer
какой канал и лайк это стример
with three of them we’re going just us a live channel
с тремя их едем просто нас лайв-канал
why a streamer and behind a chair and headphones
почему стример и за кресло и наушников
well, that’s how I got the impression I
ну вот так меня создалось впечатление я
just blog before from Ukraine andrey
просто блоге до из украины андрей
trying to give a damn about me while communicating with
попытка на меня наплевать общаясь с
Russians while already identifying tremeres
россиянами при этом уже тремеров
on  no eyes, just a comfortable
определяю на глаз нет просто удобное
chair and headphones, but you
кресло и наушники а вот вы украины
specifically chose Ukraine randomly  oh, the whole
специально выбрал случайно пополз вся
country crawled, the state,
страна штат
yes, all the oddities hurt, but do
да все странности больно а вот есть у
you have any questions for the inhabitants of Ukraine,
вас какие-то вопросы к жителям украины
you will forgive me, but I’ve probably been sitting for
вы меня простите но я уже сижу наверно
two hours and for another,
часа два и за другого
and I’m already very tired of this topic
и мне очень уже надоело вот эта тема
because everyone has their own truth and so
потому что у каждого своя правда и так
as I am Russian, respectively, all the
как я русская соответственно все
very good and bad words of the guys
очень хорошие и нехорошие слова ребят в
addressed to me, so I don’t want to, I
мой адрес поэтому я не хочу я сюда
came here not to swear, so
пришла не ругаться поэтому
I’m neutral because I don’t
я отношусь нейтрально потому что не
relate to politics and having, in principle,
отношусь к политике и не имея в принципе
no right to talk about it, probably
никакого права об этом наверно
not in the sense that  us
разговаривать не в том плане что у нас
russia russia there somehow you
россия россию там что-то как-то у вас
have swallows of a citizen of the
есть порождает ласточек гражданина
russian federation of
российской федерации
course you already belong to politics you
конечно вы уже относитесь к политике вы
are endowed with political rights
наделены наделены политическими правами
and that she I don’t want to talk that
и что она я не хочу разговаривать то
is, but I don’t have any
есть но я же не имею какие-то
duties to talk here less
обязанности разговаривать здесь менее
you can see you say that I am out of
можно увидеть вы говорите что я вне
politics in politics, well, because if
политики в политике ну потому что если
there are some such political directly
какие-то такие политические прямо
in-depth questions, I don’t understand them, it
углубленные вопросы я в них не соображаю
just turns out to be a body  visor, I don’t watch the
просто получается телевизор я не смотрю
newspaper, I don’t read what’s
газета я не читаю что
interesting, that is, I’m
интересно то есть я
two pieces of herd people for numbers, two
двое шт им людям табуна за числа две
reptiles to sit in roulette with a Ukrainian and
гадины сыдыть в рулетке с украинцем и
yours are all tortured there, shorter than 67 scarlet
замучилась ваши все там короче 67 алого
at the junction, I remove Ukraine, why, well,
на стыке убираю украину почему что ну ка
I’ll come up with their feet  they would
я придумает их кто-то ног их бы просто
just be bananas, I wanted to dug the right ones
вот бананы я хотела вырыты правильного
to clean ukraine neck 2 years of innovation
на убирала украину шеи 2 года инновации
Ukrainians come across and something shorter and
украинцы попадается и что-то короче и
tell the current smoke and button accordion and
рассказа нынешний дыма и баянных и
invalid currency quentin and the choice will be
валюты инвалидную квентин и выбор будет
let the russ get on your behalf
пусть руси получается от вашего имени
so they kill people in ukraine
так убивают людей в украине
mister me  said I don’t want to
господин я же сказала я не хочу
talk about this topic, it’s probably
разговаривать на эту тему вам наверное
better for you to find yourself another si maybe
лучше другого найти себе си возможно
they’ll let me while I’m with you if I don’t want to
дадут пока я с вами если я не хочу
break into these topics other topics no
разбить на эти темы других тем нет
cofete let’s talk
cofete давайте поговорим
what other topics to talk about let’s talk about a
какие другие темы разговаривать давайте
topic if look and other
давайте тему если выглядеть и другие
topics suggest I think  this topic is
темы предложите я думает эту тему зараз
pawing at the ass at once, well, that is, and that people are
лапает за попу ну то есть и что люди
orders, I don’t want to talk about
наказы я тут не хочу говорить про
politics here, so let's talk about something else and you
политику так давайте о чем другом и ты
mess, let's talk about what she writes  my
кашу давайте о чём она напишет свою
version, I’m a cult of this sofa at once, for
версию я культом это дивана зараз-за
prabhu, well, what topic will she now
prabhu ну и какую тему она сейчас
offer,
предложат
write now if she
напишите вот если она него она выбирает
chooses Ukraine but doesn’t want to talk about the war
украину но не хочет поговорить о войне
from another house about what’s the
откуда другого дома о чем
matter for the sake of love
дело ради любви
before we wouldn’t know to fight on any other topics
до на любые другие темы драть мы бы и не
the nature of this is like about nature
знал природа этого подобно про природу
let's talk about nature and you are
давайте поговорим про природу а вам это
interested and so I thought that you absolutely
интересно и так думал что вам абсолютно
do not want to mention about nature you want to
не желать упомяну про природу вы хотите
hear something else no look you are on
услышать что-то другое нет смотрите вы
fire I don't want about a special operation let's talk
горите не хочу про спецоперацию давайте
about nature you suggested nature let's
про природу вы предложили природу
talk about carbon apple roles
поговорим про углероду apple роли я
in general, I repeat it once again to you, it’s interesting, even
вообще раз повторяю вам интересно даже
interesting, I think that you don’t
интересно я так думаю что вам это не
see how much damage to nature has been
смотрите вот сколько ущерба природе
caused by the military aggression of Russia, I
нанесена от военной агрессии россии
’ll answer you what kind of
букле вашему отвечу вас какой под
context why are we talking about a natural
контекст почему мы про природному
trouser-leg view context like you
штанину просмотр контекст как вами
some kind of not Russia Ukraine I don’t want
какую-то не россия украина я не хочу
talk about the rights of the game is not about nature what to
разговорить прав игре не про природа что
talk about and russia let's talk about
разговаривать про и россии давайте про
russia smooth breakthrough and
россии глади прорыв и
let's talk about nature  in russia
давайте давайте про природу в россии
what do you think the war is already ready to go to
как вы считаете война уже готов ехать в
ukraine affects the environment
украины влияет на экологию
you are not married a person you are an adult
вы не женаты человека вы взрослый
yes I wanted to say 41 and I
да вот я и хотела сказать 41 и я вот вам
’m telling you that I don’t want to talk about
говорю что не хочу разговаривать про
Ukraine I don’t want to talk at the
украину не хочу разговаривать на данный
moment and you don’t care  I’m talking about
момент и вы все равно я говорю вот про
selling offers to suggest
продавать предлагает в предложите туда
your topic of problems there, I don’t want to, I
свою тему проблем я не хочу я же вам
’m telling you to find it better harder I’m already
говорю вам найти лучше труднее мне уже
fed up with these talks about Ukraine, a
осточертели эти разговоры про украину
special operation and the like, but now it’s coming
спецоперацию тому подобное а вот сейчас
out if you don’t want to say why the
выйдет если не хотите говорить почему же
game can I press it  it does
игру можно я нажму дали можно если не
n’t even forbid it’s not even forbidden they thought it’s a
запрещает даже не запрещено считали чем
problem
проблема
to let your version of who loves you
напустить свою версию кто тебя любит вам
write your versions of who this girl is,
напишите свои версии кто эта девушка так
that is, she specifically chooses Ukraine
то есть она специально выбирает украину
so she
так она
doesn’t study iodine is tormented by talk about an
не учится йода мучают это разговоры про
AIDS operation during the Brooklyn monsoon and all
спид операцию под муссонов бруклин и все
this is said by everyone about special operations all
это говорится всеми про спецоперации все
speaking in a dream, but she continues to choose
сне говоря но она продолжает выбирать
Ukraine, and then she wants something else,
украину и тут она хочет о чем то другого
for example, about nature, well, when I am
например о природе ну когда каждого я
natural  she went to the dress about nature, she can
природе она пошла на про природу может
talk, that is, and I, too, yes, it seems
говорить то есть и я тоже да кажется
clerical, like this, and start topics
конторский вот так вот и починать темы
there blah blah blah did not go in and
там бла-бла-бла не зашел и плавно
then smoothly lead to the right
подводят потом к нужным
son of food and so that you don’t have enough
сын питания и чтоб ты не хватило
talk about wilma by the power of choice yet
говорите про вильму по силе выбора еще
ukraine chose let moldova russia be there in
украина выбрала пусть там молдову россию
their image and what do you want and the moon well,
их образе своем а шо ты хочешь и луна ну
let's say there was no killer who
скажем не был убийца кого нам
happened to us does not give up to saturate
приключилась не сдается чтобы насытить
it surrounds the comfort of people just understood the
ее обрамляет уют людей просто понял
trash smelled fried so and you decided
трушке запахло жареным так и вы решила
yes she wanted to not with everyone here she
да она хотела на не со всеми тут она
understood  something, yes, I also
понял что-нибудь да я тоже так
find something like that, you know, someone there is a guy and a
находит знаешь кто то там парнишу а
girl there, we click our ears and immediately there
девочка там мы щелкаем ухом и сразу там
she opened her mouth to him, he piled on the
рот раскрыл она ему он там навали на
project there, I think something, that is, a headset,
проект я думаю что то то есть гарнитур
how would I know to give, but let's get up about
как бы я знать отдать а давайте про
nature every year  this is
природу поднимитесь каждый году это
negative
негативно
now cultural news yesterday the
сейчас новости культуры вчера был
director of the philharmonic society was brutally murdered
зверски убит директор филармонии
about the nature of this type
про природу данного типа природа тут
Only often do you
в селе я бежала насколько часто вы
say that I don’t like it, and in the
сказать что у меня не нравится и а
morning I don’t want a warehouse, I don’t want to
наутро склад я не хочу я не хочу с вами
be right with you, and well
были правы и ну ну давайте причем а
, let’s do it, and let’s go against nature, it won’t be
природе давайте против вам это не будет
interesting to
интересно я как дэнни люди олег я думаю
you  almost everyone is the
что вы им ибо чем еще почти всякий так
same action on the jit blog, although wine
самый акция блоге джиту хоть и вина ити
got caught
попался
wrote people yes he has a buff channel for the rights of
писал люди да у него buff канал за права
people there against delays and at the same time wine
людей там против просрочек а зараз вин
could change shoes and drown for power and so
мог переобуться и топит за власть и так
on so it’s you our Ivan Evsino these
дальше так это вы наш иван евсино эти
icons on salaries like a
иконы на зарплатах как и
man  organized with the flight and the
мужик организовано с перелетом и
manuals of May at my time in Omsk, before
методички мая при мне омске до
that, you recognized you by the face of our
этого ты и отмены так по лицу с нашими
people and was afraid that you
людьми на вас узнала и побоялась что
would have to merge in public, yes, it’s there,
придется слиться прилюдно да это же там
it’s okay, so after all, she’ll take you to the
это окей так ведь она принять к дьяку
clerk to think of eg and
вам задумать eg и
smoke more often one at a time  I’ll be safe
дымом чаще один за раз буду вы целы
now there will be a cheerful such ailments
сейчас будет веселенький такие недуги
aloe efflorescence video I think in winamp days the
алоэ высолы ролик я думаю в винампе дни
monastery
монастырь
at t remove the cloth please then
у т тряпочку убери пожалуйста то вообще
there won’t be any damage at all
не не будет никакого повреждений
good afternoon you what is the name of the channel
добрый день вас как канал называется
when it is called quietly x  ende accounts all
когда называется он тихо хэнде счета все
Russian bloggers are afraid to withdraw their channel,
русские блогеры боятся свой канал
what is your channel called
отзывать уж как у вас канал называется
anti-snoring there is no such thing in your tube oh well on
антихрап нету такого ю тубе да ладно на
valegro it’s not like that I’ll check now we can get on the
валегро не так я проверю сейчас можем
star you then curl get along andrey
звезду bам потом локона уживаться андрей
pop stars kabul how like andrey folder
поп-звезд кабул как как андрей папок
milena andrey popok
милена андрей попок
this account is like this  for the last name you are Polish
этот счет такой за фамилии ты польскую
that you are a Pole
что ты поляк
you don’t know Russian
вы русский язык не знаете
but butt is butt as priests
но попок это попка как священников
were called in the Russian empire in the
называли в российской империи в
Russian empire yes but
российской империи да а
now it’s different yes differently
сейчас по-другому да по другому
what was the name of the pope dads were them and
как поп назывался папы были ними а
now and now there is a holy father or
сейчас а сейчас там святой отец или
then okay  look, so that the conclusion
тогда окей смотрите дабы интерес вывод
by nationality is interesting who I look at in the USSR from
по национальности кто я смотрю в ссср из
some kind of graph the nationality of the
какой-то так графа национальность
soloists and who your mom and dad were by
солисток а кто вас мама и папа были по
nationality, too, the heart was not they
национальности тоже сердце не они не
were not from they were the Republic of China you
были с они были китайском республики вы
did not have vodka the road from where from
не имели имея водку дорога с откуда с
which region  as he said, they are also
какой области как его сказал еще
seated by andrey folders
рассаживают андрей папок
dry ass
dry попка
intellectually difficult 11 letters and this is where
интеллектуально сложно 11 букв а это где
wait in the end or where is that bi bi that bi
подожди в итоге или где ту би би ту би
right about you can now  you can find yes
прям про можно сейчас можно найти да
come on seryozha andrey
давай сережу
ass
андрей попка
like a joke before in the first class
типа шутка до того как в первом классе
there is no interest your viewers also rally
нет интерес ваши зрители тоже ралли
folders or on the sides like if you
папок или по бокам как если по-русски
write in Russian then through the letter and daddy is
писать то через букву и папик это
in Ukrainian and
по-украински и
write daddy like this with new
напишите папик вот так новыми
Russian
русский
stream rods  when choosing s3 mini food, I
удилища стрима выбирая s3 mini еду я
just have conversations in mind there is an interesting
просто беседы виду есть интересная
conversation reports
беседа доклады
until your last they are arrows here
до вашего последних они стрелки вот
it is written the last 2103 isn’t it in the
написано последний 2103 не это ли
evening and you are doing such conversations the meat
вечером и делаете такие беседы the meat
and a I’ll write something in a living cell
and a мне в живую клетку
20 hours ago
20 часов назад напишу
show me how you
что-то тут показывайте как у вас
are  -the troops are here and the
какие-то войска тут а
bayraktar is somehow knocking down the
байрактар что-то там сбивает как бы
Russians at the outposts of trouble
русских по заставам беды
oh it’s scary so scary very scary you
ой страшно так страшно очень страшно вы
specifically chose the date of the box for Ukraine of
украину специально выбрали дату клеточки
course of course but for what is
конечно конечно а для чего вот какая
your motivation immediately they
ваша мотивация сразу подписываться не
won’t subscribe from don’t subscribe don’t we don’t
будут от не подписывайтесь не нам не
need that  the signing of libya mom people
нужно что подписание ливии мама люди
decorated the same and so who will look will
украшали же и так кто будет смотреть
look but the Ukrainian of the ussr will elect i
посмотрит а вот украинец ссср изберут я
call heels i took up signing if i
зову кренится я занял подпишусь случае
write down fr  om show the youths what the
если бы записать from покажи отроков чем
rubbish of this shows what Krakow
показывает хлам этого вот чем кракова
is like this is what you have already read and what
вот так вот что вы уже прочитали а что
is written there
там написано
that you didn’t forgive, didn’t have time, you can’t see the
что не прощал не успел не не видно
campaign of the case, the camera
поход дела не очень ум работает камера
doesn’t work very well, it’s just not quite clear
просто не совсем четко и
and raise the T-shirt higher it wouldn’t hit the
выше поднять футболку бы не попадает в
camera
камеру
[  laughter]
[смех]
you make kid jokes for class 2 3 I’m a
детские шутки делаешь на класс 2 3 я
little cooler I’m doing 5 6 for a
чуть покруче я на 5 6 делаю сутки
day just the opposite
как раз наоборот
6 we are now a little more trimmers on the
6 мы сейчас еще чуть вас триммеры на
knife university level jokes
ноже шутки университетского уровня
will start
начнутся
you are good and breaks not you were born in the
вы хорошо и разбивает не ты рожден в
ussr but I think like you are not  I am 81 years old
ссср но я думаю как и ты не я 81 года ты
what
какого
I am
я
and
и
really really just have young people there
реально реально просто есть молодежь там
put on themselves here and the real USSR from
надевает на себя вот и реальные ссср от
how I will tell you what you remember about
как я расскажу чем вот тебе запомнилось
life in the USSR
жизнь в ссср
what you remember well yamaguchi Russian
что знать запомнилась ну ямагути русском
no why cool hugs I can tell you
нет зачем крут объятиях я могу тебе
only from the stories of my
рассказать только по рассказам своих
parents  and grandfathers, come on, here’s
родителей и дедов а давай да вот
grandfather’s tales, yes, that’s what was cool in the
дедовские сказки да вот чем круто было в
USSR,
ссср
well, I’m not going to tell you now,
ну я сейчас не буду этого рассказывать
because it’s better to say
потому что лучше скажи
you put on a T-shirt born in the
ты напялил на себя футболку рожден в
USSR, but what’s with  the USSR was such that you were
ссср а что в том ссср такова была что ты
proud of it
этим гордиться
I
я
was completely different
была совсем другая
people were other societies
люди были другие общества
if you sat down in dreams were normal and
если вы сели в сны были нормальным а
now you grew up a [ __ ] like it’s different
сейчас выросли дебилом как это другие
what if now the cheese was different
что если сейчас сыр был другой был
to be with you if now was
чтобы с вами была если сейчас был до сих
still with me yes
пор со мной да
I  like in the gulag,
я типа в гулаге
I just saw a dude dude dude it’s a
я просто увидел чувак чувак чувак
pity shorter in the tag our USSR from me so
жалко короче в тег наш ссср от я так
burnt mana it became good to live with noise
обожженных маны вот шумом хорошо жить
after 91 so I fell apart
стало после 91 так я по вот развалились
on the sole where I came up and are cool like a
на подметка куда подошел и круты как
dude and what was your life
чувак а шо у тебя было в чем жизнь на
socially  turned on so these are all the
социально включалась так вот эти все
ussr with the flukes of the ussr auto I don’t know how
ссср с сосальщики ссср авто не знаю их
to name them correctly
правильно назвать
seed April shhss aram like that was there and
сид апреля тссс арам типа вот там был а
what was there I 10 rocky having lived in that ussr
что там было я 10 рокки пожив в том ссср
that well it’s my dytyna at a time the
та ну его нафиг моя дытына за раз
finances of the noise family because with 2 engine and
финансов семьи шумов ведь с 2 engine и
you know their food we would have lived until now the USSR
знаете питание их бы мы жили до сих ссср
food whose lips we have in open access
питания чьи губы у нас в открытый доступ
to the Internet
до интернета
with Arab prices
с с арабскими цен
let's say the
скажем
topics laser
темы лазерными
orders showed the society was the poor
порядками показан общество было нищих
to live the apse was a friend the prison of peoples the
жить апсиды было друга тюрьма народов
whole world has long been alive  no, in the 21st century, arthas was
весь мир давно живет 21 веке артаса
reached in the twentieth century on wot-fan
достигали в двадцатом веке на wot-fan'е
to not be affected hours before the rest
к не затрагиваться часа до остальных
stuck in the Russian empire so that
застряв в российской империи так тот
island in Kievan Rus up to 100 staggering
остров в киевской руси до 100 шатаясь
they always think that it was better
они всегда думает что раньше было лучше
to wait earlier and the picture can be dented and you
подождать и картинка можно помята и ты
damn it all at once  I’ll find it by smished and for a
блин за раз я найду по smished и
second I want to seem like I wanted to
секундочку я хочу показаться захотелось
show you one picture, you can
вам показать одну картинку можно воины
all the warriors bachila and
все бачила и
on the right of this diamond cutter
справа данной огранщик
like
как
so so and the
так так так а
axis of the picture is called it used to be
ось картинка называется раньше было
better
лучше
it’s worth a man and even in the office when it
это стоит мужик да и в офисе когда
used to be better
раньше было лучше
those brush
те кисть
watches there are very 119  the visit of an aristocrat
часы там весьма 119 визитом аристократ
used to be better right away the knights used to
раньше было лучше сразу рыцари раньше
be better and then and how tim is in the riser
было лучше и тогда и каким тима в стояк
now nishtyak just like that and you have their savka jerking off
теперь ништяк вот так само и усих ты их
so he and everything at least a little to the
савка дрочит так он и все хоть чуть до
place so that I will get my weekdays out and
места чтобы буду ваты мои будни вон и
wants to return and poverty there c so
хочет вернуться и скудость туда c так
I know it myself, so you will be different
сама знаю так вот ты будет иную
sometimes during school it was cool it was cool
иногда раз протяжении школе было классно
in the kindergarten it was cool at the university
в садочку было классно в университете
it was cool we are adults they live
было классно мы взрослые люди они живут
here we are you have a job here  ya but we
вот мы у вас есть работа семья но нам
want to go back earlier it was better we
хочется вернуться раньше было лучше мы
were students and before there was a school he
были студентами а раньше была школа ему
ran around the garages with
бегали там по гаражам
friends and under siege there were no problems at all
друзьями а под осаде был вообще проблем
you just live and hurry
небыло сидишь только живешь и спешит
food you play yes these are the top 3 bar of
пищи играешься да вот такие топ 3 бар
ruhata 7 weekdays of ruhata in steam from Anna
рухаты 7 будни рухаты в пар от анны
Lake  you let it go, well, cool ice was
озеро ты спусти ну вот там cool ice было
good, but nikola’s whip will not turn the
хорошо хлыст же николы не повернет
past will never return, you will never
прошлое никогда уже не вернет никогда
need to look only into the future of
нужно смотреть только в будущее
ukraine, the dykes live we don’t know already in
украины дайки живут уже не знаем уже в
20, you almost put the exit like this
20 другому чуть ли не ставите так выход
street to live and
улица жить и
technology piece intel work that
технологиями штучный интела работа то
film  it’s just that down from the grass for this
фильм просто а вниз из травы на это
centuries and the stable medieval
веков и стабильному средневековому
caught over them and the chic option, yes, he
застал над ними и шик варианта да вот
writes on even the present time what happened
пишет на даже нынешним временем что было
what happened in the past will remain in the past
что было в прошлом останется в прошлом
so the song is a gift for 1 8 but I read your
так песня в дар за 1 8 но почитаю ваши
comments to
комментарии
glitch chatak mugs a second
глючить чатак кружки секунду
so let's  turn on the ensign of estonia on
так давайте включите прапор эстонии на у
ours today and the friendly wedge estonia and at a
нас сегодня и дружная клина estonia и за
time we succumb to one video and
раз мы сша поддаемся один ролик и
swear words
похраем слова
so 8
так 8
halva loops we hurry if t  you don’t understand the
халва мы спеши если ты не понимаешь
principle afghan in stone afghan can’t
принцип афган в каменной афган не может
write through afghan
написать через афган
this is Russian nerds night words there
вот это русский ботаны night слова там
afghanistan through the letter f can
афганистан через букву f на может
write
написать
like this write heads will punish the river
так написать головы накажет реке
frost it was funny these icons yuri
морозова было смешно этих эти иконы юрий
frost two you before frost pension seams
морозов два вы до морозова пенсия швы
danka temples short video  and the
данька дужек короткий ролик и
dishonest side of the maali like this caught the
нечестными стороны маали вот так попался
ear great
уху велик
exactly the fly was taken away
ровно муху увели
he reached the letters in the boat, let's at least
он дойдя в лодке букв давайте хоть и
rejoice what are you saying you were glad where is
чё ты говоришь вы порадовались где вот в
the chance to joke now where good
том что шутите шанс сейчас где добрый
afternoon yesterday good afternoon today I am great with you
день вчера добрый день сегодня я с вами
where I understood you
здорово где я понял у вас
when
ограничениями возможности
there are such characters, I go out to
бывают и такие персонажи мне выходит к
their patrol there, and now you
их там patrol а ты сейчас
[laughter]
[смех]
go to the fact that there is a tycoon from Ukrainians,
выходит на то что там магнат из украинцы
and
так
so it happens that
вот и таки бывает
we jump to the tick and intellectual
прыгаем до тиковые и интеллектуальные
parts of our
части нашего
today's
сегодняшнего
stream violently for a year and today we
стрима яростно году и сегодня у нас у
have today
нас сегодня
so
так
friendly outskirts of estonia and today we are
дружной окраина эстония и сегодня мы по
facing pro and rack moss and, without
сталкиваемся про и стойку мох и , без
two corners so
два угла так
up to fold 1
до раза 1
skilki is ma  I will find both the words of
скильки это мая найдешь и слова
Estonian and language how many letters are kept
эстонского и мовы сколько букв держатся
in the longest word of the Estonian language a
в самом длинном слове эстонского языка
question without Google for skilki liter May you
вопрос без гугла на скильки литр май
will find from the word
найдешь из слова
Estonian pier and how many letters are contained
эстонское мол и сколько букв содержится
in the longest word of the Estonian language
в самом длинном слове эстонского языка
so she who guess who else
так она кто угадай кто бы еще
so
так
I led chevy 14  little 45
я вела chevy 14 мало 45
hydroelectric power station is already in Beijing
гидроэлектростанция уже в пекин
so let's find skilki
так давайте скильки
beech in May and you will find the words of the Spanish
бук в мае найдешь и слова испанской
hammer to go, that is, who to wake them up in the
молот ехать то есть кто на их будить по
morning the baby no one gave the exact
утрам малыша никто не дал точные
correct view and
правильные видповиди и
let me keep the intrigue right now literally
давайте я щас держу интригу буквально
seconds knight and
секунд рыцарь и
give and correctly view for me  drunk and
давать и правильно вид по ведь я пьян и
I will voice this word scarlet, but my
буду озвучивать это слово алого но моя
42 liters forty-two letters
42 литра сорок две буквы
c to the
c слову
word,
вот
let's voice the
давайте мы озвучим
word and so it's like late tea and that the
слову и так якось поздно чаем и что в
artist's kit or
художник комплект или до
home in the other half of the day after the day
дома в другие половине дня после дня
people Zhenya in the spirit of days like this I don't know
народ женя в духе дни вот так я не знаю
what if there is someone from Pistonia so
че если есть кто-то из пистоний так
tell us about this word like where
расскажите нам про это слово типа откуда
it came from exactly
оно именно такое взялось
[music] is
[музыка]
quite interesting so here are the facts about the
довольно интересно так я вот факты про
history of
истории
Estonian  oh language in
эстонском языке на
where such
откуда такая
forty miles of cheaters 2 letters there is a battle in the form of a
сорок миль читеры 2 буквы там битва виде
bulan
булана
yes it turns out to
да получается
become such words you came up with
станьте такие слова придумал
you want to say
вы хотите сказать
you but about the thread of the mouse at a time sayings are
вас а про нить мыши за раз поговорок
smart and mean pony al hayat show you video is being
умен и виду пони аль хаят шоу вас видео
recorded update update vidosik and
записывается обновить обновить видосик и
c and subordinate our group  guess the melody
c и подчиняем нашу group угадай мелодию
so in gadot and the words of the river
так в гадот и слова реки
Estonian new year, but the words
эстонскую новый год же польше слова
to count from the word mean and it’s worth
напустить счет со слова означают и стоит
kimovich
кимович
write what do you think this word
напишите что вот это слово по вашему
means in Estonian
означает в эстонском языке
to run a version of someone’s word but
запустить версию чьи-то слова но
means in persistent mother
означает в стойкий маме
irina
ирина
Estonian 15 cases 3  the
эстонском языке 15 падежей 3 долготы
length of the sounds of vowels and consonants life
звуков гласных и согласных жизнь это
is the same as in Hungarian to the Bugor
также также как венгерском на бугорский
sea,
море
fly the January region down and a prayer
лети январским области down и мольба
ready so they will immediately say for now I
готовеньким так сразу скажут за сейчас я
picked up words that are consonant with
подобрал слова которые созвучны и со
some Slavic languages and you can see there are r
славянскими некоторыми языками и видно
serves from these languages \u200b\u200bthis word is vik but t
есть запасы чение из этих языков это
e windo
слово
is open  a
вик но окно open a
words aken original stop
слова акен изначальной остановки
maverick but
maverick но
let's share one more word right away i
давайте поделимся еще одно слово сразу
'll say it like this words  and silently xii
скажу это так слова беззвучно xii
Slavic new and c words after the
славянскими новыми так и c слова после
same to put on your hand from the
таки напустить на вашу руку от еще
words in the Estonian sea
означается слова в эстонский море
I will be correct everything we
буду правильного все
succumb and kim and linguists
поддаемся и ким и лингвисты
for almost the version this word means
на почти версию это слово означает
Estonian my
эстонский мой
idol to answer the same kind yes
идол ответить тож вида да
then trouble gave the word
то беда дал слово
thread thread thread
нитка нить
word in Estonian is more insulting than Jacob, but
слова в эстонским обидней якова но
we sound cleaner on the butt of the sea of keys of carved new g
мы почище на прикладе море keys резных
oups, as they are close from the residence of the peopl
новых групп як близки из проживания
in front
народе
and lexical material in the mind
передъ и лексический материал в инж
f the mind, so we
умову
l, okay, we swear further on the words
так ну так окей ругаемся далее снов
of the word, so we still have a sonorous sound behind the Slavi
слову так еще у нас тут звучная за
mole and we give for now
славянскими молом и даёте мы
the words
пока слова
we are almost
мы почти
and
и
what does it mean there is this word on sts.  and the
что значит есть это слово на стс . и
hammer
молот
pedal of the date is it necessary whether the alarm flowed
педаль даты надо ли набат протекала
discounts on deir for yes you
скидки на дэир по да ты
didn’t give a
не дала
week a week an
недели недели
anguish and share the correct view for
надрыв и делимся правильный вид по ведь
you,
ты же
that is, in Russian a week for
то есть по-русски неделя на
you cindy
вы синди
bassem that we have how sonorous to
бассем что у нас как звучно до
Slavic give him maybe poked to the
славянскими дать ему авось тыкала до
point  someone
сути кого
on the hot ones, that is, profit, and although you can
на горячих то есть выгода и хотя можно
be ashamed of the light, twist the linguists at the place of
его стыдно свет крути лингвисты месте
catching the
отлова
frame frame in the check from here she will try to
рама рама в чек из тут она попробует
benefit you from the word try to guess what
выгода ты c слова попробуйте угадать что
in Estonian this word means
на эстонском языке означает вот это
frame frame without knowing the right
слово рама рама не зная правильно
choice,
выбрать
I would not have guessed right away
я бы не догадался сразу скажу
that is, the
то есть
hand you knew about the
рука вы знали на
aroma yes, strike you there is no aroma delicious
аромат да рази вас нет аромата вкусный
aroma
аромат
let's dvp this word
давайте двп это слово
world
мир
guilt their sonorous scarlet moon came the
виновность их звучно алая луна пришло
appearance of the word lameness actresses the words book in
вид слова хромота актрис слова книга на
Estonian this fragrance
эстонском языке этот аромат
aroma went veterans merged
аромат пошло ветеранских слитами хромота
lameness chi can this be on the Slavic word doctors
чи можна это на славянское слово врачи
let's rise
давайте поднимемся
flavor magic create when grammar grant
аромата создать когда грамматика грант
on
на
even literacy by badge nick note
даже грамота по значка зарубка заметка
on it turns out here both that
на это получается сюда оба что
literacy grammar c  ms is rare and youth
грамота грамматика cms редко и молодость
has gone and like this half a word book
пошло и вот так потро полуслова книга
aroma we will continue far aiza once the words are
аромат продолжим даль айза раз слова
like tsska you but I think it can be with 5
такие цска вы но я думаю ее можно с 5
sonorous intercessor
звучным ходатаем
you a
вас словечко
word it also means worth klimov today we
еще оно означает стоит климова сегодня у
have a day in Kalym from the year they are on the
нас день в калым из году им на стриме
stream Estonia as friendly  to ukraine the idea of
эстонию яко дружную на украину идейку
ory to give the
культуры историю
program you
дать
were also not guessing well, although ag
программа ты была так же не угадаешь ну
in the letters would have to be rewound thi
хотя снова грамотам нужно было бы
word of thousands shark like
перемотал это то слово тысяч
his versio
акула типа
we have food these people go one cover versi
этой версии у нас еды эти люди идти одна
n higher and here bachu is rich is rich the ri
кавер-версии выше и тут бачу богата
ht kind will win like this with
богата правильный вид победит так с
site for it was just not to the word but
сайт за было просто не к слову а
at the same time
зараз
buda buda
буда буда
troshka of these cells cheburek bloody
трошки этих клеток чебурек кровавого
king for stories bans the seams will
королю за рассказы банами швы будут
spam the new
спама новом
roller care Russians along the way so 8
валике заботу российские по ходу так 8
turk
turk еще означает
also means the word turk spanish
еще означает слово turk
little ode what here teak
испанскую мало одре чего сюда тиковый
tick-tock tick avu versions  our hearts
тик-так тик аву версий наши сердца
august him
август него xrp
xrp turk
turk
type
тип
yak-yak hit
як-як удар
hit
удар
[music]
[музыка]
the same
тот же
glory market to the bazaar no word on the bargain
славу рынок на базар нет слова на торгу
from this someone to guess trade
от это кто-то токто догадаться торговать
tour during  you by the sleeves and a quote, the back of the
тур воды вам за рукава и цитату спина
screen is his words, but he quickly makes
экрана его слова но до спешно составляет
hits, and the folding axis will be the word alla,
хиты а ось складная буду слову алла
you can find her, you can find vip prominent,
можно найти ей можно найти vip видных
similar in sound, our muscle is
схожий по звучанию наш мышца
small, vividly, Nazara words, so we have,
малом живо назара слова так у нас
as we had 1 time everywhere,
как у нас был 1 раз повсюду а
well, who  cool linguist try in
ну кто крутые лингвист попробуй в
ukrainian language both in russian
украинской мове оба в российские
sniper retinue of prominent try yes who
снайперки свиту видных попробуйте да кто
cool linguist in ukrainian or russian
крутой лингвист в украинском или русском
language will find some
языке найдет какое-то
correspondence
соответствие
doctors what they want ask cats type of
врачи их чего хочет прошу коты вид
duty you throw exploded not
повинности вы кидаете взорвалась не
sounds 30 or cyprus and voice
звуки 30 или кипр и голос
give a hint in ukrainian condition
даю подсказку в украинском условие
jumped take it down yourself
прыгала снесите сами
in the Russian word further in the Russian or
в русском слове дальше в русском или
Ukrainian word all agree the
украинском слове согласны все те же
same as here
самые что и тут
I’ll
я
cut down the hint, I’ll bring the gates to us, well,
волосни у нас доносит врата ну вот
try to say a new rotan and you
попробуйте сказать нового ротаны и вы
now understand the account of the
сейчас разумеет и счет
dotsenko, but both coils
доценко но оба катушках
oh here shifts in your mouth to  there we
ой тут перекладывает во рту на там
rejoice from the moon
радуемся с луны
[music]
[музыка]
ku-yes war thunder you are on the coil yes there
ку-да war thunder ты на катушку да там
yours that in rich words jumped from does not
твой что в богатых словах прыгал из не
lose and the voice of them is m  to change and for 1
лишается а голос них же менять и за 1
pdk a powder, life flows with a
пдк рошке жизнь течет
delivery of a plus sign to become like a thunderstorm once it
поставкой плюсиком уподобиться гроза раз
starts itself on there is a tin such
начинается сама на есть жестяк такая
nemo has signs in our hammer
nemo имеет признаки в наших молот
persha words tse
перша слова це
yak by charter
як уставом озвучить
we help out and today we are visiting us on
мы выручаем а сегодня у нас в гостях на
our aspire estonia we grow on a cone
нашем устреми эстония мы растим на конус
drive will hand over and  let others tell us the
приводом сдадут и пусть другие нам крины
history there culture and suffer and the axis
историю там культуру и страдаете и ось
today we have estonia and there are such words
сегодня у нас эстония и есть такие слова
from two years old sounds and 6 medium and and
с двух лет звуки и 6 средних и и
consciously the number of
осознанно число
olaf your heart you think like that damn I
олаф ваше сердце вы такие думать блин я
scored points you are attached to for us and
набрал баллы вы крепится на для нас а
for the son and
для сына и
no one  while it looks like reptiles, but it’s correct to
никто поки на вид гадов а правильно
branch not so that the Estonian tank
ветвиться не чтоб танечку эстонские c
c sounds
так звучит
like this
вот так
Aleksashin xor we swear further,
алексашин xor ругаемся далее
we already know that c is a thread, but
мы уже знаем что c нить а
just words in hot.  Yes, and all the
просто слова на горячих . да и все
checks, if
проверки вот коли таком
I love your humor like this, so let
люблю ваш юмор так давайте
me know at my mother’s hundred I work
я знаю у матери сот сама работаю
from
от
us right, so you go to us and you knew from the slave
нас правл так вы нам хода и ты от раба
Abu, you both
абу знал ты оба
pros wat against there work the
профи вата противо там работу the
pot sa word
pot sa слову
to work and now we start to live poke
работать а теперь начинаем жить тычок
even  for 1 share
даже за 1 акция
omit the words which means
опусти слова что означает
you can immediately guess from this word of
тут же можно догадаться по этому слову
creation
творения
you can unload the logic of the word of creation
можно выгрузить логику слова творения
they
их
are work what will be
есть работа то что будут
what and elbows twitter what tekke only
чем и локтями twitter чему текке только
mova many times we had Lithuanian so
мова много раз у нас было литовском так
let the words sleep sonority to
дайте слова спит звучности
ours so today we have  visiting
нашим итак сегодня у нас в гостях
estonia and tulum from year life tony and the
эстония так и тулум из году life тони и
most tool to the fashion historian lads you knew
самый tool историку моды братвы ты знала
that I still could up to the prices is called yes it
что я таки смог до цен называется да
turns out some work here
получается нечно работа вот
personally
лично
worked as a guide gave
работала гидом дали
night work dpr
ночная работа дпр
attacks and find
атаки и find
who will say what this word means dodiga stalin
кто скажет что это слово означает додига
sea
сталинский море
there  you can guess
там можно догадаться
here and iksha let yourself clean work the date
тут и икша пусть сами чистая работа дата
was sometime father's work
была нечно работа отца
[laughter]
[смех]
turns over leaving the working thread
получается над покидая рабочая нить
fix
починить
yana can wash out the
яны может вымываться
work of the night  but if the price is scarlet we pedo
работа ночи но если цена алая мы pedo
march
марша трошки
troshka I will not seem to guess the faces of the
я не буду казаться чтобы подгадал лица
word
слову
just but the doctors you know her scarlet so within
просто но врачи вы ее знаете алая так в
the framework of acquaintance with the thin new
в рамках знакомство с тонкой новую так
so and meaning lead on the enemy so vsc the word
вот и означая лид на врага так vsc слово
late tea edge and
поздно чая край а
what does this word mean
что означает это слово
out of 4 we don’t know what they were called
из 4 мы не знаю как их называли
my page needs to be washed
моя страница работать надо мыть
like this for 300 years brightly this is a joke I am
так-то 300 лет ярко это шутка я я
c so
c так
mother is aigyr krait t everything everything is
мать есть айгыр крайтом т все все богат
rich rich forgive me it’s just the
на богата простишь это просто
edge of the edge of the flight to the edge of the ice
краю кромка лёту на край лед
on the edge of the people there on the move  but the project is like
на краю люду там на ходу но проект так
that, although I would give up until you want there the
то то хотя сдавалась бы до хочешь там
pole from the tundra, and so on, the car is not
полюсе из тундра и так далее еще авто не
on
на
either, so I don’t think that you will be
тоже так я не думаю что вы будет
digitized such a commission of the jury of the date
оцифроваться такое комиссия жюри даты
will give ridgid audi I’m going for continuous months,
даст ridgid audi я иду слитных месяцев
because what Estonia says is often
ибо чем в эстонский молвит дуже часто е
repeated  before
повторения до
kycok, does derpy fight in twos, and
kycok ли дерпи драться-то по двое не и
it doesn’t come out in 4, but
выходит по 4 не выходит а
castim dug the owner, you know 30
кастим вырыли хозяин вы знаете 30
pages in my opinion, she wouldn’t know these
страниц по моему она этих бы не знал
with buttons, denoted by google, me and rob, and
кнопками обозначал google мы с робом а
not in order to at least up to 4, but the skin
не для того чтобы хоть до 4 а кожа
plays for sam  P  erevesili writes or I’m a
играет для сэма перевесили пишет или я
lawyer by education in my first
юрист по образованию по первому
education I’m a programmer in my second and a
образованию я программист по второму и
sheet, but they don’t work as a lawyer to earn
лист но юристом не работают зарабатывать
a living and a programmer, and he
на жизнь и programmer так и он же у нас
ended our today’s
закончилось наше сегодняшнее
Estonian after you give so and there and
эстонские после даете так то там и
thought Estonia there to study karina e
загадывала эстонию там учиться карина е
to e friendly  friendly people of ukraine and
к е дружный дружный люда украины и
today she was visiting us
сегодня она у нас была в гостях
to let in who is for whom places two all our
напустить кто за кого места двое вся наш
stream
стрим
i masturbate the arch and even the
я [__] арку и даже пришел дан ответ
pony natalie
пони natalie
kozh came back, let's say padikovo on parta.ua so i
kozh скажем падиково на parta.ua так я
think we will try to work our
думаю мы будем стараться с работы наши
streams and our channel  babyliss professions to
стримы и наш канал babyliss профессий
us so why am I hot already having decided on a
нам так почему я горячий уже вы решив на
lavalier microphone having chosen a special one
петличный микрофон выбрав специальный
close I will also take such professions
закрыть еще возьму такие профессии ные
for streamers we
для стримеров
understand the trifles of the necessary for misha to
разбираемся трошки нужного for миша
drink sound with spare panels for them to
пить звука запасным панелями для чтоб их
be on the alert dam ladies ruhaty his
она была начеку дамба дам рухаты его его
you are on our information about steven against
ты на нашей информации о стивене против
sex bots are given to honor someone with language
ботов сексе дано почтить кто зыковым
places 2 our stream is boring, that is,
места 2 наш стрим надоевших то есть
very seeing reading
очень видя читая
this icon to
эту икону
blogger petr i mat and  it can be thrown by a
блогеру петр i mat и его может закинуть
donat,
донат
maybe,
может
but you want to, seeing something there, it’s
а ты шо вы хочет видя че-то там вам
convenient for you to look st, who
удобно смотрим ул еще эти кого
else do you still tear off for dogs ares on
еще вы отрывает еще для собак арес на
so maybe peter and motives mind on a
так может и петр и мотивам умом на на
cup to the choice of what else we’re cool and
чашечку к выбору чему там еще мы cool и
target them  the product so tell you and that
створе им продукт так и скажи вами и что
we want the fur coat to develop like grass its
мы хочем шубин развивался как трава его
petr and mod and ours we will be in this
петр и мод и наши мы будем в этой стики
mind stick and those alignment and there the oligarchy look the
виду и те створе и там олигархии вид
behavior of large corporations so the scoop
поведение крупные корпорации так д совок
looks at you will be up to the stream will we
смотрит вас будет до стрим будет мы
added with faxes may suffocate  and we
добавили с факсами мая удушат и и
’ll talk the other day to reasonable bloggers,
поговорим буду на днях разумным блогерам
but I recorded
же записал
with rob wood the
с робом
same look at the carved blogger at the robot,
вудом таки огляд резных блогере в робота
that’s right and musya glory to ukraine
вот прямо и муся слава украине
someone was from
единичку в чате если кто-то был из
Estonia, it’s interesting or today
эстонии вот интересно или на сегодняшнем
3 but because we had people and
3 а потому что нам прошлом были люди и
oaths in the past and we just had about Lithuania and
клятвы и у нас как раз была про литву а
here it’s interesting put a one in the part
тут интересно поставьте единичку в часть
if you were from a source it’s interesting to
если вы были из источник интересно
see
посмотреть
[music]
[музыка]